Guide to the Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, records
1965-2010
MS 1971
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
434.92
(999 boxes)
The Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, records consist of drawings, photographs, correspondence, and other materials documenting a selection of the firm's built and unbuilt projects.
Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects
Gwathmey, Charles, 1938-2009
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as received by the donor. To locate a specific project and its related records, please consult the project index.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
Conditions Governing Access
The bulk of the materials are open for research. Several residential projects, indicated as "anonymous" in Project Index, may be used by researchers but the clients not identified in any published or unpublished medium. See project index for details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Bette-Ann Gwathmey, 2010-2011.
Scope and Contents
The Gwathmey Siegel and Associates Architects, LLC, records consist of drawings, photographs, correspondence, and other materials documenting a selection of the firm's built and unbuilt projects from the 1960s to 2010. Projects include art and educational facilities, such as the Yale University Art and Architecture Building addition and the Burchfield-Penney Art Center in Buffalo, New York; corporate and institutional projects like the IBM Corporation Office Building and Distribution Center in Greensboro, North Carolina, and the David Geffen Foundation Building in Beverly Hills, California; and residences and interior design conversions such as the de Menil Residence in East Hampton, New York and the Dunaway Apartment in New York City. The records do not include materials generated by the firm, which became Gwathmey Siegel Kaufman and Associates Architects, LLC, after Charles Gwathmey's death in 2009.
Biographical / Historical
Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects, LLC, was founded by Charles Gwathmey, Yale School of Architecture, Class of 1962, and Robert Siegel in New York in 1968. The firm's residential work, large institutional projects (such as Whig Hall at Princeton University, an addition to the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum in New York, and the American Museum of the Moving Image), and renovations of existing buildings (including the Henry Art Gallery at the University of Washington and the Fogg Art Museum at Harvard University) have earned numerous awards and honors, including the American Institute of Architects' Architecture Firm Award and the Lifetime Achievement Award from the New York State Society of Architects.
Architect-designed houses -- United States; Architecture -- United States -- History -- 20th Century; Architecture, American; Architecture, Domestic -- Designs and plans; Architecture, Postmodern -- United States; Gwathmey, Charles, 1938-2009; Siegel, Robert (Robert H.), 1939-; Gwathmey Siegel & Associates Architects; Gwathmey Siegel Architects
- Project Records, 1965-2010
  General
  Gaps in box sequence are intentional.
  Other Finding Aids
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - Gwathmey Residence and Studio, 1966
    Scope and Contents
    Job number: 19-6501
    Job location: Amagansett, NY
    Project type: Residential
    Client: Gwathmey
    - Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 3)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 1–3, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 3)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 1–2)
  - de Menil Easthampton Residence, 1983
    Job number: 19-7914
    Job location: East Hampton, NY
    Client: de Menil
    - Correspondence (Box 3, Box 61)
    - Specifications (Box 61)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 63, Box 2072)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 3)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 3, Box 63, Box 65, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 61–62, Box 65–66, Box 71–73)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 64)
  - de Menil Houston Residence, 1979
    Job number: 19-8108
    Job location: Houston, TX
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 67, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 69)
  - de Menil Santa Monica Residence, 1981
    Job number: 19-8202
    Job location: Santa Monica, CA
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 70, Box 2072)
  - Gagosian Residence (Originally de Menil Residence
    Job number: 19-9828
    Client: Gagosian
    - Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 3, Box 75–76, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 77)
  - San Onofre Residence; Casale Residence (9522), 1997
    Job number: 19-9321
    Job location: Pacific Palisades, CA
    Client: San Onofre ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 3, Box 181–182)
    - Correspondence (Box 3, Box 181–183)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 182)
    - Specifications (Box 3, Box 183)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 181–182, Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 3)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 193–194)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 3, Box 181, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 183–186, Box 190–191, Box 194)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 3, Box 187–189, Box 192, Box 195)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 189, Box 192)
  - Sedecca Residence, 1968
    Job number: 19-6701
    Client: Sedecca
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 11)
  - Straus Residence, 1966
    Job number: 19-6602
    Job location: Purchase, NY
    Client: Straus
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 11, Box 63, Box 65, Box 73, Box 461, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 11, Box 461)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 11, Box 461)
  - Whig Hall
    Job number: 19-7002
    Job location: Princeton, NJ
    Project type: Education
    Client: Princeton University
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 21, Box 63, Box 65, Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23–24)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 22, Box 25)
  - Tolan Residence, 1970
    Job number: 19-7005
    Client: Tolan
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 31, Box 2071)
  - Cogan Residence, 1972
    Job number: 19-7105
    Client: Cogan
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 41, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 41)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 41)
  - Taft Residence, 1980
    Job number: 19-7721
    Job location: Cincinnati, OH
    Client: Taft
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 51, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 51)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 52)
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum: Renovation and Addition; Auditorium (9516), Masterplan (9525), Sackler (9717), Modifications (0515)
    Job location: New York, NY
    Project type: Museum
    Client: SRGM
    - Background and Reports (Box 81–86, Box 90, Box 92)
    - Design Development (Box 83, Box 87, Box 89, Box 91)
    - Correspondence (Box 84–85, Box 88, Box 91)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 85, Box 88, Box 91)
    - Specifications (Box 87)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 86, Box 114, Box 2072)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 81, Box 83)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 92–107, Box 117–118, Box 130)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 63, Box 65, Box 113, Box 137A, Box 139A, Box 140, Box 141A–141B, Box 142A–142B, Box 143A–143B, Box 144–145, Box 2072, Folder 137B, Folder 138)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 108–112, Box 116, Box 121–123, Box 125, Box 127–129)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 115, Box 118–120, Box 124, Box 131–136)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 126)
  - Oceanfront Residence, 1993
    Job number: 19-8802
    Job location: Malibu, CA
    Client: Oceanfront ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 151–152)
    - Design Development (Box 151–152)
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 151)
    - Specifications (Box 152)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 152, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 153–154, Box 161, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 153, Box 158)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 155–157, Box 159)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 160)
  - Zumikon Residence, 1994
    Job number: 19-9012
    Job location: Zumikon, Switzer-land
    Client: Zumikon ANONYMOUS
    - Correspondence (Box 171–172)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 173–174)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 175–177)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 173)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 178)
  - Malibu Residence; (9209, 9610, 9611, 0108)
    Job number: 19-9710
    Client: Malibu ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 202, Box 204)
    - Design Development (Box 202)
    - Correspondence (Box 201, Box 204)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 201, Box 204)
    - Specifications (Box 203–204)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 209, Box 214, Box 220)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 205–207, Box 209, Box 221, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 208–209, Box 211, Box 218–219)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 210, Box 212–218, Box 222–227)
  - Hilltop Residence; Annex (0012), 2009
    Job number: 20-9215
    Job location: Austin, TX
    Client: Hilltop ANONYMOUS
    - Background and Reports (Box 231, Box 236)
    - Design Development (Box 231)
    - Correspondence (Box 231, Box 233–234, Box 236)
    - Meeting Minutes (Box 235)
    - Specifications (Box 232, Box 236)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 237, Box 243–244, Box 248–249)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 231, Box 239, Box 242, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 238, Box 240–242, Box 254–257)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 243, Box 245, Box 250–253, Box 258–259, Box 261–262)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 245–247, Box 260)
  - Library and Science Building, 1984
    Job number: 19-7902
    Job location: Middlebury, CT
    Project type: Education/Library
    Client: Westover School
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 271–272, Box 274)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 272–273, Box 2072)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 273)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 274–276)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 275)
  - American Museum of Moving Image; (9306), 1988
    Job number: 19-8310
    Job location: Atoria, NY
    Client: American Museum of Moving Image
    - Background and Reports (Box 281)
    - Correspondence (Box 281)
    - Specifications (Box 281)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 281)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 282)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 283, Box 290, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 284–286, Box 296–298)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 287–289, Box 291–295)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074A)
  - IBM Corporation Office Building & Distribution Center, 1987
    Job number: 19-8511
    Job location: Greensboro Rochester, NC NY
    Project type: Corporate
    Client: IBM
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 301)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 301–302, Box 304–306, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 301, Box 303–306)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 301)
  - East Academic Complex, Eugenio Maria de Hostos Community College, 1994
    Job number: 19-8514
    Job location: Bronx, NY
    Client: The City University of New York
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 311–313, Box 315)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 314, Box 316–317, Box 321–322, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 317)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 318–320, Box 323)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 324)
  - Werner Otto Hall Busch-Reisinger Museum and Fine Arts Library Addition to the Fogg, 1991
    Job number: 19-8804
    Job location: Cambridge, MA
    Project type: Museum/Education
    Client: Harvard University
    - Background and Reports (Box 331)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 332–336)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 336–340, Box 2073)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 338–340)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 339, Box 341–345)
  - Social Science Building & Super Computer Center (9304), 1995
    Job number: 19-9107
    Job location: La Jolla, CA
    Client: University of California at San Diego
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 353, Box 355)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 351–352, Box 355, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 353–354)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 356–362)
  - Henry Art Gallery Renovation & Addition, 1997
    Job number: 19-9302
    Job location: Seattle, WA
    Client: University of Washington
    - Background and Reports (Box 371)
    - Design Development (Box 371)
    - Correspondence (Box 371)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 371, Box 2076)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 371)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 372)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 373, Box 375–376, Box 2076)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 374–377)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 377–381)
  - Campus; Sports Facility, Academic/Cultural Center, Campus Research Facility, 1999
    Job number: 19-9312
    Job location: Singapore
    Client: Nanyang Polytechnic
    - Background and Reports (Box 391)
    - Design Development (Box 391)
    - Correspondence (Box 391)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 392)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 392–395, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 393–395)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 394, Box 396–397)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074A)
  - Levitt Center for University Advancement, 1998
    Job number: 19-9325
    Job location: Iowa City, IA
    Client: University of Iowa
    - Background and Reports (Box 401, Box 411)
    - Design Development (Box 401, Box 411)
    - Correspondence (Box 401, Box 411)
    - Specifications (Box 411)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 401, Box 411, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 402)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 402, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 402–403, Box 405)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 403–404, Box 407–410)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 406)
  - University Technology and Learning Complex, 2001
    Job number: 19-9606
    Job location: Southfield, MI
    Client: Lawrence Technological University
    - Background and Reports (Box 421)
    - Design Development (Box 421)
    - Correspondence (Box 421)
    - Specifications (Box 421)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 421, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 422, Box 425, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 423, Box 425)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 424, Box 426–428)
  - The Jewish Children's Museum, 2004
    Job number: 19-9815
    Job location: Brooklyn, NY
    Client: Tzivos Hashem
    - Background and Reports (Box 431)
    - Design Development (Box 431)
    - Correspondence (Box 431, Box 442)
    - Specifications (Box 432)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 431, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 434)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 433, Box 2075)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 436–437)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 435, Box 438–441)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 437)
  - Goldberg Residence, 1968
    Job number: 19-6802
    Job location: Manchester, CT
    Client: Goldberg
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 471, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 471)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 471)
  - Cooper Residence, 1968
    Job number: 19-6803
    Job location: Orleans, MA
    Client: Cooper
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 481, Box 2071)
  - Dunaway Apartment, 1969
    Job number: 19-6904
    Client: Dunaway
    - Correspondence (Box 451)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 451, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 501–502, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 503)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 501, Box 503)
  - Steel Residence I Bridgehampton, 1971
    Job number: 19-6805
    Job location: Bridgehampton, NY
    Client: Steel Residence I
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 491, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 491)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 491)
  - Steel Residence II Bridgehampton, 1971
    Job number: 19-6905
    Client: Steel Residence II
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 511)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 511)
  - SUNY at Purchase Service Group and Heating Plant, 1972
    Job number: 19-6914
    Client: State University of New York at Purchase
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 521)
  - SUNY at Purchase Dormitory, Dining & Student Union Facility, 1972
    Job number: 19-6900
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 531, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 531)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 532–535)
  - Breslow Apartment, 1971
    Job number: 19-7101
    Client: Breslow
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 541, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 541)
  - Cohn Residence, 1972
    Job number: 19-7201
    Client: Cohn
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 551, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 551–552)
  - Friday Barn, 1973
    Job number: 19-7300
    Job location: Greenwich, CT
    Client: ANONYMOUS
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 561, Box 2071)
  - Pearl's Restaurant, 1972
    Job number: 19-7301
    Project type: Interior
    Client: Pearl's Restaurant
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 571, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 571)
  - Malibu, California Residence, 1973
    Job number: 19-7303
    Client: Geffen ANONYMOUS (Private)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 581, Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 581)
  - David Geffen Headquarters Office/Foundation Building at 331 N. Maple, 2000
    Job number: 19-8909
    Job location: Beverly Hills, CA
    Client: Geffen Foundation
    - Background and Reports (Box 591)
    - Correspondence (Box 591)
    - Specifications (Box 591)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 591, Box 2074)
    - Articles and Awards (Box 591)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 592–593, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 592, Box 594)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 593)
  - Geffen/Salick Office Building at 411 N. Maple
    Job number: 19-8911
    Client: Geffen/Salick
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 604)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 601–604, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 604)
  - Geffen/Salick Office Building at 407 N. Maple, 2003
    Job number: 19-8921
    - Background and Reports (Box 611)
    - Correspondence (Box 611)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 611–612)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 611)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 612)
  - Universal Studios at 331 N. Maple (Originally The David Geffen Foundation Building), 1999
    Job number: 19-9604
    Client: Geffen/Universal Studios, Inc.
    - Background and Reports (Box 591)
    - Design Development (Box 591)
    - Correspondence (Box 591)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 591)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 621–624)
  - Apartment 17 AB, 1978
    Job number: 19-9605
    Client: Geffen (Private)
    - Correspondence (Box 631)
    - Specifications (Box 631)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 631, Box 633, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 632–633)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 634–635)
    - Drawings: Interiors/Millwork (Box 632, Box 634)
  - Maple Associates LTD at 407 N. Maple (Originally Geffen/Salick Office), 2003
    Job number: 19-9810
    Client: Geffen /Maple Associates LTD
    - Background and Reports (Box 611)
    - Design Development (Box 611)
    - Correspondence (Box 611, Box 641)
    - Specifications (Box 611)
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 611, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Historical Documents/Site/Surveys/Landscape (Box 611)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 611, Box 2074)
    - Drawings: Construction/Submission Documents (Box 642–647)
  - Haupt Residence, 1977
    Job number: 19-7610
    Client: Haupt
    - Photographs and Slides (Box 2071)
    - Drawings: Sketches/Studies/Presentation/Concept (Box 651–652, Box 2071)